Current planet: Mars             Target engine: Solar Sail [r][r]

Since solar sails need to rely on sunlight as a source of propulsion energy, [r]
Therefore, the closer it is to the sun, the more suitable it is.
So we have to build solar sail modules on Mars as engines to go to the Jupiter-like planetary belt. [w]

Solar sail, [lr]
Reflect the light from the sun or other sources through huge film lenses, [r]
The light irradiated on the mirror surface generates radiation pressure through the reflection of photons to provide thrust. [lr]
In this way, as long as the sun continues to shine, the solar sail can continue to operate. [w]

In the solar system, the most suitable task for solar sails is to circle around the sun[r]
(E.g. observe the polar regions of the sun at close range) [lr]
There are plenty of photons there, and the sail has the highest efficiency. [lr]
Therefore, at this stage, most sails must include the high temperature environment in the factors that must be considered [w]


In terms of manipulation, [r]
Adjust the angle between the reflected sail and the sun, [r]
The direction of thrust received by the spacecraft can be changed correspondingly in the control, [lr]
Therefore, when the solar sail propeller is advancing, manipulating or controlling the flight attitude, [r]
No need to consume fuel [w]


In terms of restrictions, [r]
Before the solar sail reaches sufficient speed, it must pass through several months of accumulation [lr]
And the volume is very large, but the load is very small in comparison. [w]

The world's first solar sail-powered probe was IKAROS launched by Japan in 2010[r]
 (Interplanetary Kite-craft Accelerated by Radiation Of the Sun)[w]

The key technologies of IKAROS are [r]
"Large-area membrane solar sail", [r]
"Whether the thin-film solar cell embedded in the solar sail can start the payload instrument", [r]
"Measure the acceleration generated by the radiation pressure on the solar sail", [r]
"Variable reflectance LCD panel controls navigation posture" [w]



Currently necessary parts are scattered all over the planet[r]
Next, all you have to do is to collect the parts of the engine[r]
There may be difficulties in the process, and your ingenuity is needed! [w]

[solar]